[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Helena] You know,
when your phone blacks out,
it means it's been cloned.
-That's impossible, Madam.
-Shut up!
[Lily] I'm sure Red Dragon already knows
that I'm her enemy.
[Arnaldo] I've been having some
thoughts lately. About a woman.
-Well, what do you see?
-Lustful things towards her.
Where did you get this, by the way?
I found it inside the Bible
Grandpa gave me.
Madam, we've traced the IMEI number
of whoever tapped Mercedes' phone.
She was right. The one
behind all this is Lily Cruz.
I missed you, so I was thinking… lunch?
I was just thinking
of the exact same thing.
[Julio] Why are you furious?
Is it because Arnaldo is slowly
starting to remember Ivy Aguas?
[Diego] Ivy Aguas is dead.
Both she and the old Arnaldo!
I want you to kill Diego Torillo now!
[Lily] I'm done playing pretend,
Helena Montoya.
So now, I'm going to make sure
you admit it yourself.
That you are none other than Red Dragon.
[Diego] Nanny, don't tell
Uncle Pandoy, okay?
I bought him his favorite cake.
[Ivy] Wow, Mama. The fish tastes amazing.
It's not fish.
It's snake.
[Helena] I made it.
Emilia told me you have
a fondness for snakes.
[Lily chuckling]
Of course, Emilia.
By the way, I'm curious.
Were you born in the year of the snake?
[tense music playing]
No.
No, Mama.
I think
it was the year of the dog.
And, you know, I read something.
I hope you weren't born
in the year of the dragon,
because dragons and dogs
are mortal enemies.
[tense music swells]
[chuckling]
I really wouldn't know because
I don't follow these things.
But you know what? Speaking of dogs.
I don't really like them
because they are so needy
and manipulative.
You know, they play nice and cute,
but when you turn around, they bite you.
[chuckles]
Yes, Mama.
Yes! It's true.
That's what dogs are like.
But, at least, they're loyal.
Like, when someone thinks
to hurt their loved ones,
that's when they attack.
I still think they're pathetic creatures.
[tense music playing]
[Jose] Hmm.
You know, you're a good cook.
[Jose scoffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
Poor Diego.
He'll be surprised when he comes back.
What do you want from us?
What do you want?!
Shh.
Let us go!
-We didn't do any--
-Shut up!
[Loring exclaims, cries]
Shut up!
[breathes heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Pandoy sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[phone ringing]
-Sanggano?
-Sir.
[Jose] We're all set.
We're just waiting for Diego.
Good.
And don't forget…
to bring his corpse to me.
Yes, sir.
[stutters] Diego?
-What will you do to Diego?
-Diego.
We already did what you want.
Isn't that enough?!
[Loring cries] Don't kill Diego!
Not him, please! No… Not Diego.
-What did I tell you? What did I tell you?
-Not Diego, please.
-I told you to shut up!
-[Loring screams]
-[Jose] Well?
-We're begging you!
-Hey, you two.
-Not Diego!
Keep an eye on these two here.
-[man] Yes, boss.
-I'll take care of Diego.
-Not Diego!
-Don't! Please, not Diego!
-Sanggano!
-We'll take care of them.
-Sit!
-Son.
-I said sit!
-Sanggano!
-Sit down!
Sit down, or I'll use this gun on you!
-[Loring] Pandoy.
-Sit down.
And shut up.
Diego.
Oh!
By the way, I hope you don't mind.
But you have to refrain
from calling me "Mama."
Emilia's getting a little jealous.
Got you.
-[upbeat music playing]
-[Lily laughs]
Oh, Emilia! What's new?
That's nothing new, Mama--
I mean, Helena. That's nothing new.
Your daughter has always been so insecure.
Well, okay.
So, I guess I'll just call you
by your first name.
Yeah, sure. Just call me "Helena."
No.
No. Helena is too long.
Can I just call you…
"Hel"?
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
That's so funny.
[Helena] Oh!
I almost forgot.
I have something to show you.
It'll just be a while.
I hope you don't mind.
Yeah, no problem.
[tense music continues playing]
I guess the boss took a long walk.
It'll probably take him a while.
Do you want to smoke?
What about these two?
Don't worry about them.
They're too terrified to run away.
Let's go before the boss comes back.
[man 2] Just stay there.
Don't even try to escape!
Or else you'll both get it.
[Pandoy coughs]
-Pandoy!
-Don't be so loud! Please!
Here.
What are you-- What should we--Huh?
-Pandoy.
-Wait? Wait. Ouch.
-Okay. Okay…
-We need to…
-My goodness.
-Hang in there!
[Pandoy] Hang in there.
-[Pandoy breathing heavily]
-[both struggling]
-There. It's done.
-[Loring groans]
[Loring groaning, crying]
Come on, come on! This way.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio chuckling]
Mister Goody Goody Gumdrops!
It's only a matter of time, grandson.
The black sheep will soon be sheared.
[suspenseful music continues]
-[Pandoy panting] Come on…
-[Loring crying]
-Pandoy.
-Loring. Loring.
-[Loring sobs]
-Loring, let's go. Come on.
Diego!
-Diego! Diego!
-Nanny! Uncle!
-Diego!
-[gunshots]
Loring! Run, Loring! Run!
-Hey!
-Run! Run, Loring!
[gunshots]
-Pandoy! Pandoy!
-Uncle!
[Loring] Pandoy! Pandoy!
Pandoy! Pandoy!
[gunshot]
-[Loring shrieks]
-[Diego] No!
-[Diego] No! No, no!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[Diego] No! No! No!
-[Loring wailing]
-[gunshot]
-[Loring shrieks]
You bastard!
[thuds]
Get over here! Bastard!
[grunting]
[Diego grunts]
-He's mine!
-[man] Stop resisting!
[screaming]
You bastard!
[Diego screams] You monster!
[Diego groaning]
[Diego] Bastard!
[thuds]
-Give me your gun.
-[man 3] Mr. Diego!
-Give me your gun!
People are coming.
Boss, we have to leave!
-They're coming.
-Let's go, boss.
[grunts]
[man 1] They'll catch us here. Let's go.
[Diego groans]
[car engine starts]
[car doors close]
Nanny. Uncle.
-[breathing raggedly]
-[unsettling music playing]
[Diego grunts]
[Diego breathing raggedly]
Help.
Help us!
Nanny. Uncle.
Nanny. Nanny!
[melancholic music playing]
Nanny.
Nanny. Nanny! Nanny.
Uncle.
Nanny!
[melancholic music playing]
[Diego screaming]
Help!
Please help us!
Nanny. Nanny, please. Don't leave me.
Uncle!
Help!
Help us!
Someone, please!
Help!
Nanny!
[man] Mr. Diego!
[women crying]
Nanny. Nanny.
Nanny. Uncle, hang in there.
Nanny. Uncle. Nanny.
-[women crying]
-[woman] Loring.
[women crying]
Mr. Pandoy! Miss Loring!
-Help. Please help.
-Help us!
Let's bring them to the hospital! Hurry!
Mr. Pandoy!
Hurry. Let's bring them to the hospital.
[overlapping conversations]
[woman] Miss Loring!
[women crying]
[melancholic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
You really are a filthy dog.
I turn my back for one second
and off you go rummaging through my house?
Go, Mama. Go!
A change in costume
and hairstyle too.
Are you going to a party?
I have nothing to hide from you now.
That's right.
Because I know you bombed my properties!
And you sabotaged my shipment.
An eye for an eye, Red Dragon.
[tense music]
They say…
you're indestructible.
[Helena chuckling]
Let's see…
if you don't melt from my fire.
[dramatic music]
[Helena struggling]
Try me.
[Helena groans]
[Helena groaning]
[tense music playing]
[Helena gasps]
-Well? Aww!
-[Helena panting]
[Lily] What's this?
Is the Red Dragon shivering in fear?
[dramatic music]
[breathes heavily]
Why?
Are all those needles deadly?
Are they poisonous?
Huh?
-[Helena grunts]
-If that's the case,
then this is farewell.
Goodbye, Helena-Montoya-slash-Red-Dragon!
[Helena screams]
Ma.
[whimpers]
[suspenseful music]
[Lily] Hmm!
[laughing]
Why so scared, Red Dragon?
Do you think I'd kill you with needles?
No!
You know what you deserve?
Hmm?!
What you deserve is
a slow death that eats at your soul.
You deserve to feel every ounce of pain!
You'll suffer so bad and so much
that you'll long for death, instead!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Helena gasps]
Goodbye, Hel.
[screaming]
I would've killed that dragon
if I didn't have principles.
I would've pierced those needles
straight through her neck.
But then, we both know
how that woman is above the law.
She's even worse than the Ardientes…
which means I'll have
to resort to violence.
Lily, it won't be that easy.
She's a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Well, Mom,
she made an enemy out of me,
so I'm going to expose her.
I'm going to expose
all her crimes to the world.
[upbeat music]
[Helena] You think you can terrify me?!
I am Red Dragon…
and I will kill you, Lily Cruz!
Prepare to die burning!
[laughing maniacally]
[groans]
[groaning]
No. No, no, no, Helena!
No!
There's no reason to fear Lily Cruz.
You are Red Dragon!
You are going to drag that woman to hell!
Mercedes!
What's going on here?!
Can you please let me in?
I need to speak to my mother
because I'm going to help her
shred Lily Cruz into pieces!
So, let me in!
Red Dragon can't see you right now.
Excuse me.
And, I meant that literally
because I have to go.
Hey! What's happening?!
Red Dragon is fine. She wants to be alone.
Oh, yeah right.
And who are you to tell me what to do?
For the nth time,
Red Dragon doesn't want you
to know her location.
So, please, silence.
[scoffs] Silence? Why?
And who are you again?
You're just Mama's sidekick. A servant.
And, let me remind you, I'm her daughter.
So, let me in!
[Jose] Governor.
[Julio chuckles]
-Sanggano.
-Governor.
You imbecile!
-Governor, please, stop!
-Please, stop!
Governor.
Let go of me!
Just look at yourself.
You're as purple as an eggplant!
You look like a bruised fruit!
There's no doubt in my mind
that you failed!
Maybe it'd be better
if I buried you instead,
so I can put an end to all my problems!
But Governor…
I was able to kill his foster parents.
-So what?!
-Governor, stop it, please.
Stop acting so smug. Are you deaf?
I told you to kill Diego Torillo!
Not his useless,
old peasant foster parents!
Diego's the one
who's ruining all my plans!
I couldn't care less about those two!
Looks like they're all you can handle.
Hey, you. Go clean yourself up.
You're a disgrace!
Now, I don't care…
if you go blind.
Or deaf. Or even if
you lose an arm or a leg.
Because I'm not letting you die
until you finish the job
I asked you to do!
Now, get out!
You reek of defeat.
Scram! Go fix yourself.
Leave, all of you!
What a bunch of idiots!
[scoffs] Some colonel he is.
He's nothing but a useless bastard.
[Diego] Nanny.
-[doctor] Ambu bag.
-Hang in there.
-Sir. Sir.
-Wait.
Wait, I'm not leaving.
-We'll do everything we can.
-Nanny.
Please wait outside, Mr. Torillo.
Nanny. No, I'm not leaving.
-Sir. Sir, sir.
-Diego. Diego.
Mr. Torillo.
-Doc!
-We'll do everything--
Doc, please do everything you can.
-Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
-Please, doc.
-Please wait outside.
-We trust you, doc.
[doctor] Continue CPR. Insert IV line.
[somber music playing]
Nanny Loring, Uncle Pandoy…
we still have so many dreams.
You can't go yet.
[somber music continues playing]
[Jepoy] Lily? Lily?
-Aunt Camia, where's she?
-Jepoy.
[Lily] Jepoy, what is it?
Did something happen?
Mr. Pandoy and Miss Loring…
they're in the hospital!
In the hospital? Why? What happened?
Sanggano shot them.
[gasping]
Those vile Ardientes.
I just know they're behind this.
Sanggano is one of their men.
What they did is just unforgivable.
Loring and Pandoy never did
anything to the Ardientes.
Mom, I need to see Diego.
I'm sure he's feeling twice
the pain that we are now.
I need to see him.
I need to be there for him.
-Is the car ready?
-I'll start it up.
[somber music playing]
[doctor] Sir.
I'm so sorry.
We did everything we could,
but they'd both lost too much blood.
-No, no, no, no.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-Sorry--
Nanny! Nanny.
[somber music continues]
Nanny.
[weeping]
[sobbing] My Nanny…
Nanny.
Nanny, I love you very much.
[somber music continues]
Uncle.
Uncle, I love you so much.
Uncle, you can rest now.
[bleak music playing]
Come here, Diego.
[Pandoy] We're sorry
about what happened earlier.
[Diego] I should be the one apologizing.
[Loring] It's a birthday party, right?
Enough with the drama.
-[Pandoy laughs]
-[Loring] We should be happy.
[Diego] Well, I know
I wasn't being dramatic.
[dramatic music playing]
-[fist thumping]
-[breathing raggedly]
[gunshots]
[Loring] Pandoy! Pandoy!
[Loring shrieks]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music continues]
They'll pay for this.
They'll pay for this!
[Emilia] Stop it! Let go of me!
You can't kick me out because
this is my mother's house!
And you! This isn't over, Mercedes!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
This isn't over, Mercedes!
[Emilia groans]
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Madam, your daughter just left.
I told her exactly what you said.
Yes, Madam. I'll be there.
[upbeat music playing]
Madam.
You have a new mission.
You have been trained
to be my best fighter.
And now is your chance
to display your skill.
Kill Lily Cruz.
But, Madam, Lily Cruz knows
you are Red Dragon.
For all we know, she's already
working on an exposé.
How will we get rid of her
when we know
she's also plotting against us?
Relax.
You're the soldier, and I'm the brains.
Until the last drop of her blood spills…
until she draws her last breath…
I'll plan her demise.
I just need for you
to execute the perfect crime.
I want you to kill Lily Cruz.
[ominous music playing]
[unsettling music swelling]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
[thumping]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
Lily Cruz. Lily Cruz. Lily--
Who are you really?
I don't understand. I haven't met you,
but I can't stop myself
from thinking about you.
I always see you…
in my dreams.
I don't understand what's happening.
Why do I feel like
I've known you for a long time?
Why do I feel this way for you?
I'm so confused.
Why does it feel like
I'm in love with you?
Doc, how are Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy?
How are they doing?
I regret to inform you…
they didn't make it.
They were brought to the morgue.
Excuse me.
[somber music playing]
Mom, where's-- Where's Diego?
Where did Diego go?
Where--
Where could he have gone?
[exhales]
Wait, I think I know.
Where's Julio Ardiente?
I need to talk to him.
Let me in.
I'm sorry. We can't do that.
I need to talk to him. He called for me.
-Sir! Sir!
-Julio!
Sir! Sir, wait.
[Diego] Julio Ardiente! Julio!
[guard] Sir! Sir, wait.
Julio Ardiente! Come out…
[Diego] Julio!
[guard] Sir! Sir, wait.
[Diego] Julio Ardiente! Come out!
-Face me!
-Sir! Sir! Calm down, sir!
-[Lily] Diego!
-I'm here!
-Diego!
-Show yourself!
-Come out!
-Diego!
-[guard] Sir! Sir!
-Come out and face me, you bastard!
Let go of him! I said let go of him!
-Diego. Diego.
-Diego, that's enough.
[Jose] Sir!
Let me shut that clucking hen up.
[Julio laughing]
Who are you calling a clucking hen?
Look! Look at him. Look at that kid.
He's fuming with rage,
like a fierce rooster in a cockfight,
waiting to be unleashed,
ready to kill anything in its way.
Diego, what are you doing here?
You're putting yourself in danger.
-I know what I'm doing!
-No. No, you don't.
What you're doing now
won't do you any good.
-Come on. Let's go home.
-Then what?!
Tell me, how should I feel…
when they killed my foster parents?!
I know.
Julio Ardiente's life won't be enough
to pay for everything he's done!
-Diego, I know. Diego!
-Hold on!
-Diego!
-Follow him!
You.
You are the clucking hen
because you can't even silence
that rooster out there.
-[Julio scoffs]
-Governor!
Give me this one.
I'll show you who's going
to be the last man standing.
Last man standing?
You're like a parrot…
that won't shut up.
Change of plans.
Use your head!
Do you want me to be suspended again
before I even get back to the capitol?
Governor, this is the perfect
time to get rid of that pest.
He might be a pest.
But we're going to do it right this time.
I have a better plan.
This is going to work.
[Julio laughing]
This will be fun.
[Julio chuckles]
[Lily] Diego.
[tense music playing]
-[Jepoy] Diego.
-[Lily] Hey!
-Jepoy.
-Diego.
-[Lily] Let go… Let go of him.
-[Jepoy] Let go of him.
Diego.
[tense music continues playing]
[Julio clapping]
My!
Your performance is what…
people of my age would call "fiery,"
or…
people of your age would call…
"lit."
You bastard!
Why did you drag them into this?
They were innocent!
Diego, you're…
making up things out of…
thin air.
You know what?
Try backing up
your accusations with the truth.
Because if you can't do that…
you're nothing but a street magician who--
-Diego.
-You bastard!
Diego!
-Diego!
I'll kill you!
-You bastard!
-No, don't!
-Papa!
-Jepoy!
-Hey! Get out…
-Diego!
[Diego growls]
[Julio coughing]
You monster!
[Emilia shrieking]
Stop it!
You bastard!
-Hey!
-You…
-Diego.
-Oh my God. Papa!
Diego. Diego.
Get out, you bastard!
[Emilia] You're all trespassing!
[Julio coughing]
Take him to jail!
You saw what he did!
He was going to kill me in my own house.
[Julio coughing]
What are you waiting for?!
Take him outside! Do it, now!
-[Lily] Diego.
-[Emilia] Well?!
[Raul] Hold on. What's this?
-I'll kill you!
-Hey! Hey! Hey! Wait!
Let go of my son! What is this, huh?
Why are you doing this to my son?
He didn't do anything.
Shut it, Raul! I saw it with my two eyes!
He pushed Papa! I saw it!
[Lily] Do you know why he did that?
It's only because your father
had Miss Loring and Mr. Pandoy killed.
[tense music swells]
Papa, is this true?
-No.
-Liar!
Whatever that is, stop it!
Don't ever hurt my son, Emilia!
-Fine, then!
-[Emilia] Get out of here!
Then go with your son!
Take them both to jail!
-You should be the one in jail!
-Blah!
Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah!
Take those savages away!
Yeah, get out!
I promise you this, Julio Ardiente…
[Diego] You'll pay for what
you did to my foster parents!
[scoffs]
I'll bring you down!
-That's enough. That's enough!
-Take him to jail!
-Enough!
Now, Ardientes.
See?
See, Julio Ardiente?
With every person you hurt,
fate itself will drag you down.
No. I didn't kill--
Drop the damn act!
Because you can never deceive me.
I know you had them killed!
And because of what you did to Diego,
you just declared another war.
Oh.
The question is…
are you ready for one?
There's only one way for you
to find out, Julio Ardiente.
[tense music swells]
Try me.
Get out…
-of my house.
-And you?
Don't you point at me!
I will point at you--
This is my house!
-You know what?
-[Julio] Enough, enough.
Why don't you visit
your dragon of a mother?
Yes, Emilia, your mother is scared
because I know everything.
How Helena Montoya is Red Dragon!
Oh.
I see. But you need to leave our house.
Leave! Get out, all of you!
-Now!
-We will!
You don't have to repeat yourself.
We wouldn't want to stay in a
house full of murderers, anyway!
[Julio] Typical…
Why are you still here?! Get out! Now!
-We're leaving!
-[Julio] It's enough!
-Right now!
-[Julio] It is enough!
-Now!
-It is enough, Emilia!
It is all right.
-What?
-Leave them be. Leave them be.
Leave now!
[tense music playing]
Hey, officers! Don't just stand there!
Get rid of these trespassers!
[Raul] We're leaving.
[Emilia scoffs]
Get out!
What?
You believe them?
That I had them killed?
-[Emilia laughing]
-You like it, huh?
-Mm-hm.
-[Julio laughing]
Well done.
-Thank you.
-[laughing]
[Julio] These people never learn.
Never mess with Julio Ardiente…
and Emilia.
[both laughing maniacally]
[both exhale heavily]
I will kill them! I will kill them!
-Diego.
-Just let me do this!
Diego, wait.
Listen to me first.
I know how it feels, Diego.
I know how much your heart is hurting.
But please.
Diego.
Diego, don't be so reckless, please.
Don't let your anger get the best of you.
What do you want me to do?
They killed my foster parents.
Of all people, you should
be the one who understands
because you lost your loved ones too.
Your father and Nanny Carlotta
were killed…
all because of them!
They need to die.
Yes, you're right, Diego.
We both lost our loved ones
all because of the Ardientes.
The pain and anger you feel right now,
I know them well
because they're still in my heart.
But, Diego, you know
that I can't kill anyone!
If you want to seek justice,
I'll help you.
In the right way.
My family and I will help you.
I'm the one who lost my foster parents,
so I'll do it my way.
So, please…
Please stay out of it.
I can't do that, Diego!
Because I'm scared!
If you could only see yourself right now!
It's like you're ready to kill,
and I won't let you do that!
I won't let you turn into
a criminal, Diego!
But there's no place for justice
here in Ardiente!
You know that!
So, let's stop fooling ourselves.
I will kill them.
-Diego, don't. Please.
-I will kill them!
-Diego. Diego, no. Diego!
-[Jepoy] Diego!
[door closes]
[tense music playing]
[Diego] The old Diego Torillo is gone.
All that's left is a man thirsty
for the blood of his enemies!
[Georgina] We have to secure an advantage
before Julio's camp does.
[Lily] And the evidence
against Red Dragon?
All pieces of evidence
are admissible in court.
We need a…
A credible witness. I know someone.
And I know where to find her.
That Torillo better be careful.
One wrong move,
and he'll meet his nanny
and uncle in purgatory.
[gunshots]
[theme music playing]